Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[Juliette breathing heavily]
[sighing. grunting]
[straining. breathing heavily]
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[breathes shakily. sniffles]
[sobs. sniffles]
Mmm.
[sighs]
[groans]
[Marnes] Should've known you'd be early.
You look tired already.
I was hoping to meet Juliette Nichols
before you keel over.
We'll see who gets tuckered out.
- After you.
- Thank you.
[alarm ringing]
[ringing stops]
[grunts]
You dead?
Bet you wish you were.
Come on. you're late.
[Juliette breathes deeply]
How did you get in here?
- [Mechanical worker] Your door was open.
- [sighs]
You threw up in the hallway.
And by the smell of it.
pretty much everywhere.
- Could you talk about something else?
- Oh. you mean something other than vomit?
You don't want me talking about puking?
- [chuckles]
- [Juliette] Go.
[Mechanical worker]
Why you wearing that again?
You gonna tell me what's going on? [sighs]
You're not a drinker. Jules.
Not a good one. no.
- Here.
- [Juliette sighs]
Hey. come on. Talk to me.
[Juliette sighs]
[rattling. rumbling]
Shit. My fix is failing.
- Water?
- Sure.
Here.
Unless you dumped water to lighten
your load. I think you got a leak.
[Marnes] You wanna say hello to the judge?
[sniffles]
But you do want her goons to be sure
and see you standing here.
[thudding. rattling]
Hey!
- [object clangs]
- Get out of there!
- No. I... I was just gonna do s...
- No!
- Juliette. how am I supposed to learn...
- No! Enough!
[Mechanical chief]
You wanna tell me what's going on?
'Cause I'm at a damn loss.
You told Cooper to go in.
Was I supposed to wait for you to show up?
- Really incredible smell. by the way.
- You know my rules.
Your rules?
Last I heard. I'm the head of Mechanical.
and you're my shadow.
Though I can't remember the last time
you actually listened to me.
- Only I go through the hatch.
- So you feel okay about decking Coop?
Jules. he's your shadow.
The kid fucking worships you.
It's my job to make sure it's running.
And you care so much
that you showed up two hours late.
We're putting off the inevitable.
We have to shut it down
and make a real fix.
Jules. I can't be the first guy
in the history of the Silo
- to shut the generator down.
- Better it happen on our terms
with the backup running
than the rotor shattering...
Even an hour in darkness
will be utter chaos.
- Nothing compared to what's gonna happen...
- Jules.
It's fucking better it happens
on our terms
- than the rotor shattering!
- Jules. I'll tell... I'll tell you what.
Fucking hell. [inhales sharply]
I'll tell you what.
We'll have this discussion tomorrow
when you're not hungover or still drunk.
Go home.
Wash off whatever it is I'm smelling
and take your punishment.
You punched Cooper in the face.
You either gotta do a day
on the trash line
or work off some tickets with Walker.
Can't I just let him punch me back?
[Bernard] I was gonna come out
to applaud. Walking the Silo at...
[Silo leader] If you say "at your age."
you don't get what I brought you.
What did you bring me?
Just a little token of my gratitude
for all we've done together.
Well. gee.
I'm glad somebody's getting something.
I joined her on this march of death.
and she hasn't given me anything
but grief.
You must really want something.
Well. I might need a little help
with our friend in the robe.
Judge Meadows.
[chuckles] No. you're gonna need
a lot of help.
Her office messaged me
and said you neglected to stop by.
Do you want Paul Billings to be sheriff?
Mayor. you know me.
Doesn't matter what I want.
You just run the numbers.
Which tell me that Paul Billings
is the most favorable candidate.
Is that for the Silo. or is that for IT?
What did your numbers say about Holston?
They said he'd be a great sheriff.
which he was until he wasn't.
I wonder what your numbers say about me.
Fuck the numbers. You brought brandy.
What do they say about Juliette Nichols?
She's an engineer in Mechanical.
Oh. I know who she is.
- I don't need her numbers. She's a thief.
- Thief?
Her record's clean.
She stole four boxes of H57 tape
reserved for IT.
- She stole tape.
- [Bernard] Not just any tape.
Heat tape we use to prevent our servers
from cooking.
And honestly.
the problem isn't what she stole.
- It's the fact that she stole at all.
- Bernard. she was Holston's pick.
Mayor. you can't seriously consider her.
Deputy.
- Doesn't matter what he thinks.
- I'm just the escort.
I don't like Judicial's choice
being shoved down my throat.
Mayor. bringing me a bottle of brandy
is not going to help you
win a turf battle with Judge Meadows.
It's good brandy.
It could be from the before times
for all I care.
Here are some other numbers
you should consider.
Every hour the Silo is without a sheriff.
the probability of catastrophe
increases by one point.
While we're sitting here chitchatting.
frightened citizens are arming themselves.
because they don't know
who's going to protect them.
Billings is a good choice.
Just make him sheriff.
and leave walking the Silo to kids
with nothing better to do.
[child] She's coming.
She's coming.
[all clamoring]
- Couldn't help yourself. could you?
- So I sent word.
They need us now. Sam.
[citizens] Mayor! Welcome to the Mids.
- Welcome to the Mids. Mayor Jahns!
- Hi. Hello!
I know it's been a long time
since I crossed this bridge.
In fact. I can see a couple of men
who were pimply teenagers
last time I was here.
[citizens chuckling]
[inhales deeply]
I came to look you all in the eye
and remind you how important you are.
We're all scared.
We lost a great man and a fine sheriff.
but it's this community.
It's the way you love each other
that truly holds the Silo together
even when times are tough. like now.
[citizen] We love you. Mayor Jahns.
I'm voting for you in the next election.
We're all voting for you.
[citizens chuckling] Yes.
[chuckles]
Now. I have business down below.
but I'm not gonna leave this level
till I see the babies.
[citizens laughing]
- This is Jacob. Mayor Jahns. [chuckles]
- Oh. Lovely. Very good to see you.
This is Harry.
Harry was in a hurry.
Came out three weeks early.
[inhales sharply] But he's doing well.
As I recall from your last visit.
you like to say hello
to any mothers-to-be.
[Jahns] Actually. Doctor. we were hoping
for a moment with you alone.
Oh. Oh. sure.
We were hoping to talk to you
about your daughter. Juliette.
[door closes]
- Is she all right?
- [Jahns] She's fine.
She's being considered for a new position.
- Mmm.
- Just the standard vetting.
- Any questions I can answer?
- How come she lives down deep?
[Jahns] You understand it is unusual
for someone born in the Mids
with a doctor for a father
to end up in Mechanical.
Our troubles started.
It was hard on Jules.
A loss like that...
[sighs]
She showed real interest in machines
from an early age.
Always figuring out how things worked.
how to fix them if they didn't.
[inhales deeply]
I think it felt good
to be able to fix something.
[inhales deeply] She was a little young.
but I supported her decision to go.
- How old was she when she left?
- Thirteen.
When did you last speak to her?
It's been a while.
I have new babies every week.
Jules has the generator.
It's a long walk down to Mechanical.
I can't get there and back on my day off.
I need that day to rest.
Well. If that's all.
I have an expectant mother in breech.
and I need to get baby turned around.
[door closes]
More questions than answers.
It's so hard to describe.
[Silo resident]
What you saw or what you felt?
- No. I felt fine.
- [Silo resident] Okay.
[Juliette] It wasn't the darkness
I was worried about. I. uh...
- [breathes shakily] I just felt...
- [Silo resident] Scared.
No. I didn't feel scared.
- If I was scared. I'd tell you.
- [Silo resident] Okay.
Okay. fuck. Yeah. I felt scared. I. uh...
[breathes heavily]
That much water. it's...
It was just more water
than I've ever seen.
It was more than that. [stammers]
I had just... [sighs]
You know. George. he... [sniffs]
He left me all these clues.
and I couldn't do it.
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't go down there.
- That's what I feel. I feel pissed off.
- So pissed off you took it out on Cooper.
- I don't wanna talk about Cooper.
- What do you want?
I don't know. I don't know.
I just wanna... [inhales sharply]
Run away.
It's okay. I get that. I get it.
You know. we scream. we fight. we get mad.
But every now and then.
we should tell ourselves.
- "We did what we could. We did our best."
- "We." Really? "We"?
I don't even know why I'm getting advice
from someone who sits at her bench
every day listening to the radio.
You haven't left the workshop in 20 years.
[sniffs] Twenty fucking years!
[Marnes] Did I ever tell you
about the first arrest I made?
It was right here in this park.
right over there.
3:00 a.m. Drunk. naked couple going at it.
That was my first arrest.
You know what my second arrest was?
Twenty-four hours later. Same drunken
couple going at it right there.
- [Jahns chuckles]
- It's a true story. [chuckles]
[inhales sharply. sighs]
Aren't you gonna miss it? The job?
It's time.
I was thinking that maybe I might open up
a stall in the market.
try to sell my drawings to anybody
blind enough to want 'em. [chuckles]
I honestly don't know what I'm gonna do.
I always thought Holston
would take over from me.
Compliments of Judge Meadows.
Strawberries fresh from the farm.
If you haven't tried this. don't.
One bite can be habit-forming.
Is this supposed to intimidate me?
Dessert?
No. I wanted to make sure you...
Anything swimming in
that much sugar is bad for the heart.
Then I blew it. It was supposed to be
a friendly gesture and a little nudge.
- You didn't stop by to see Judge Meadows.
- I didn't know I was supposed to.
Mayor. the second Holston went out.
the clock started
on finding his replacement.
I understand why you'd wanna pay Holston
the respect of at least meeting
with his pick.
- Oh. Bernard told you. I see.
- There really isn't time.
[Sims] Paul Billings is a good choice.
He's a family man.
dedicated. hardworking. smart.
- He cares about the people.
- Mr. Sims.
I'll make my decision
when I've completed my trip.
- Sam. you want it?
- No. Rob. I'm good.
[chews]
[Holston] Suicide is a serious crime.
[Juliette] No. it wasn't suicide.
So you've said.
- "What I was looking for."
- [rumbling]
[clattering]
Fuck. Fuck!
- [Cooper] That's not good.
- No shit. Where's Jules?
[rattling. clattering continues]
[Hank] Knox.
Madam Mayor. Deputy.
We weren't expecting you...
Everything all right?
- Yeah. It's all under control.
- [Hank] Do you want us to come back or...
[Jahns] It's not supposed to sound
like that. is it?
[Knox] No. ma'am.
[rattling. clattering continues]
- What's going on?
- The fix is failing again.
Yeah. I can see that.
- I've tried switching...
- I need to listen.
Is that her?
Yeah.
Excuse me. Madam Mayor.
- What's going on?
- [Knox] Don't worry.
[door closes]
Jules!
- The vibration's changed.
- [Knox] What?
[Juliette] It's shifted. All this time.
- the vibration's been moving it...
- This way.
- And now it's going that way.
- Shit.
- So. what do we do?
- You leave. Check the output.
Hey. everybody. back.
- Back. Come on.
- Jules. I c... I can help.
I know this generator
just as much as any...
- [Juliette shouts]
- Coop! You're her shadow.
We can't have you both up here
if this goes sideways.
Close it behind me.
This is what I was warning you about.
I know.
Good luck.
Fuck.
[clattering intensifies]
[grunts]
- [clattering stops]
- [machinery resumes whirring steadily]
Don't let her leave.
- Hey. Madam Mayor?
- [Jahns] I'll be fine.
[Silo resident] If I'd known
I was getting a visit from the mayor.
I'd have tidied up.
You don't tidy up for old friends.
Besides. you knew I was coming.
You heard it on the radio you made.
Which is so prohibited by the Pact.
I don't know where to start.
You up-toppers really don't know
your machines. do you? That's a toaster.
I was sad your marriage broke up.
Was 25 years ago.
[Jahns] I was still sad.
You and Carla were a good couple.
What happened?
[chuckles] She chewed with her mouth open.
What can I do for you. Ruth?
Juliette Nichols.
- What about her?
- I need your honest opinion of her.
Who is she. Martha?
Am I under arrest or something?
Should you be?
[door opens]
[door closes]
- Juliette.
- Uh-huh.
I'm Mayor Jahns.
Could we have a moment?
Sure.
Can't you just stay?
You got this.
[Jahns clears throat]
- [door closes]
- [sniffs]
One of my duties as mayor
is appointing the next sheriff.
One of the Silo traditions is that
the outgoing sheriff leaves a suggestion
as to who should be next to wear the star.
Holston Becker chose you.
- I'm sorry. what?
- I must tell you.
- no one wants you for this job.
- Okay.
Except for one deceased former sheriff
and me.
I know it's a lot to take in.
[inhales sharply] No.
- Pardon?
- I... I don't want it.
Hallelujah.
May I ask why?
Everyone thinks their job in the Silo
is the most important. Mine actually is.
The generator. she's not well.
And if I'm not here
to make sure she's running and...
I have to take care of her.
Well. that is too bad.
Holston wanted you to have this...
whether or not you took the job.
[Jahns] Take care. Juliette.
[door opens]
What the fuck?
[door closes]
- [Cooper chuckles]
- [Hank] Stop cheating.
Come on.
- Wow.
- That makes no sense.
You? Sheriff?
Yeah.
- Why?
- I don't know.
Because you get shit done.
- [stammers] You'd be a great sheriff.
- Coop. you don't have to suck up.
- She's not gonna hit you again.
- It should be you. Hank.
[chuckles] They'd make him cut his hair.
- Can I see it?
- Yeah. sure.
[chuckles]
You know. Sheriff Holston was the reason
I wanted to become a deputy.
I mean what do I...
What do I know about law enforcement? I...
What did you know about being an engineer?
- Not a whole lot.
- Hey. What's this?
[Juliette] Hmm?
Something's carved
in the back of the badge.
[Juliette] Mayor Jahns!
I changed my mind.
[breathes heavily]
I'll... I'll take the job.
- [Jahns] Well. that's wonderful.
- On one condition.
There's a condition?
I need to fix the generator.
[pants] I can't leave Mechanical
without knowing it's safe.
- Okay.
- And in order to fix the generator...
[sighs] ...I need to shut it down.
You need to shut down the generator?
Put us all in the dark?
- We've got a backup.
- Which provides minimal power.
Barely enough for life support.
What you're asking for.
that has never been done.
No. I...
- I know.
- People would be terrified.
People are gonna be terrified when...
When the rotor shatters.
and we're living off the backup
in darkness.
Forever.
I can do it.
[announcer] In order to repair
the generator.
an eight-hour power outage
will begin tonight at 10:00 p.m.
The Silo will be completely dark
for that period.
You are ordered to gather
in the designated safe zones
or to stay at home.
Those failing to comply will be jailed.
That's how the rotor
should be spinning. right?
So sometime in the last 30 years.
something damaged it.
- What?
- I don't know.
Maybe someone dropped
a tool from the catwalk.
- How much damage?
- All it takes is one tiny dent.
[Juliette]
That's gonna create a small wobble
that gradually builds into a large wobble.
Doesn't matter how many times
we tweak the alignment.
- It always moves out of place.
- So soon the entire thing is gonna break.
which means we can't make enough juice
to power up a single level.
let alone the entire Silo.
So how do we fix it?
First. we're gonna open it up
and see where it's broken.
Then. to fix whatever's wrong. we're
gonna have to shut down the generator.
And did you tell the mayor
we can't actually do that?
Sure. we can.
Knox controls the steam flow
from down here.
[Mechanical worker]
And if he turns it off.
how much time do you think
we'll have before it blows up?
- [Cooper] Blows up?
- [Juliette sighs] I don't know.
- I don't know. An hour?
- If you get half that. you'll be lucky.
Lemme show you why.
We don't know
what we're dealing with here.
so we've all gotta be ready.
Expect the worst.
Any issues. radio me here.
and I'll coordinate
with the other stations.
Be alert. We don't know what to expect.
Everyone be safe out there.
Molly. you and your team
head out on patrol.
- Let everyone know you're there.
- You know what to do. Let's get to it.
Hey. if it stays quiet.
there's a cot in holding.
and the sofa in my office pulls out.
- Wouldn't say either are comfortable.
- [Marnes] Good to know.
Now. could you escort the mayor
to the hostel. please?
- I'll stay here.
- No.
It'll be quiet. but I wanna know
how things are going in the Silo.
- [sighs] Night. Ma'am.
- [Marnes] See you in the morning.
[breathes shakily] As far as we know.
the Silo's never been on backup power
- and you think it'll be quiet?
- Tonight they'll just be afraid.
And tomorrow.
if the lights don't come back on?
Hope you have the combination
to the gun safe.
Hmm.
The steam comes in from way down deep.
No one knows from where.
All we know is that it comes up
through this pipe.
makes this bend.
and goes straight up to the turbine.
Now. the founders were smart.
They knew they couldn't control how the
steam behaved. so they built in a safety.
This is the containment chamber.
It protects the turbine in case
there's a sudden surge
and someone needs to regulate the flow.
You wanna stop the generator? Knox has
to close this main valve all the way.
That happens. you get about 30 minutes
before the pressure redlines.
and he needs to release it.
[Juliette] We're gonna need more time.
Can we keep it in the red?
We could if steam was cold.
but it's not because it's steam.
The more pressure it's under.
the hotter it gets.
And that pressure just keeps on building
until... [imitates explosion] ...it blows.
So. 30 minutes before redline?
At most. [sighs]
Boss?
[smacks lips] The mayor's authorized
eight hours on backup.
Once we switch over. the crew will
get to work detaching panels C and D.
[Teddy] Both?
[Knox] It's the only way
to assess what's inside.
- They must weigh...
- 1.35 tons. Each.
Guys. there's no part of this that's easy.
The slightest mistake at any point
could get somebody killed.
or worse.
leave 10.000 people in the dark forever.
Put five of our strongest guys
on each panel.
Once they're open.
I'll slow the generator down to 50%.
but I won't stop it. Not yet.
We'll identify the problem.
Then Jules will signal to me
when she's ready.
- Mm-hmm.
- At that point.
I'll shut the steam valve
and stop the generator.
Our 30 minutes starts right then.
All right?
Yep.
Now. Jules.
who do you want up there with you?
All right. Let's get to it! Come on!
Uh... Um...
[chattering]
That's right. Stay off the stairs.
Stay off the s... Back inside. please. sir.
Ma'am. ma'am... Thank you.
Go ahead.
Switching to backup.
[machine powers down]
[machinery humming]
[murmuring]
[chattering]
[generator humming]
Backup's holding steady.
Cutting steam to 50%.
- [mechanical whirring]
- [steam hissing]
[Knox into radio]
Go ahead and start on the panels.
[metallic rumbling]
It's incredible.
Okay.
That's where I gotta go.
- [electrical zapping]
- [metallic clanking]
Hey! You okay?
When we get up there.
we're gonna tuck ourselves in.
We're gonna fix what we can.
Anything larger. we're gonna send
down for them to fix. Okay?
- Okay.
- Yeah?
Okay.
- Jules!
- Yep?
You give me the word.
All right.
Go ahead.
[Mechanical worker]
Closing hatch. Our 30 minutes start now.
[thudding]
- [machinery humming]
- [gears clicking]
[gears whining]
- Now!
- [grunting]
Stop! We're here.
[Teddy] Okay!
Shit. Oh. it's bad.
Okay. [sighs. groans]
Hmm.
Okay. This blade is the problem.
We're gonna send it down.
We'll fix the rest up here.
Get the equipment up.
Teddy. bring it up!
Coop. I need you on the other side!
[breathes shakily]
Coop. I need you to check on that.
Okay. guys. It's going up now!
Come on.
[grunts]
[Juliette panting]
[Juliette grunts]
You know how I say doing things right
is better than doing them fast?
Right now. I need both.
Where the fuck is my tool?
Come on. [grunts]
Okay. Coop. Grab the other end. [grunts]
- Okay. ready? Pull.
- [Cooper] Uh-huh.
Pull. [grunts]
Yep. [grunts] Got it.
[Juliette] Send it down.
I need to fix the smaller blades.
[tool buzzing]
We're ready!
- Hey! You got it?
- [Cooper] Uh-huh.
- [stammers] I'm... I'm not sure...
- [Juliette] Yeah?
- Look out!
- [Juliette gasps]
- [Cooper] Look out! Heads up!
- [Juliette] Oh. my God. No!
- You guys okay?
- [Teddy] Yeah!
Then pick the damn thing up and get it
straight so Jules can get it back in.
[Juliette] Hey. Cooper! Cooper. focus!
I need you on the bolts. Come on. Now!
[Teddy] Go! Let's do it! Come on. boys.
[Juliette] Okay. Cooper!
[tools buzzing]
[Mechanical worker] Temperature holding.
[child] Daddy!
Daddy!
[Sims] It's okay. Son.
It's too dark.
[Sims] It's okay.
Don't worry.
The dark's nothing to be afraid of. okay?
Daddy's gonna stay here with you
till you fall asleep.
[LaFontaine] This is LaFontaine on 80.
All quiet up to the farms.
Copy that.
[door opens]
I can't sleep.
Then don't.
[Marnes] Ten thousand people
aren't sleeping right now.
terrified the power won't come back.
Afraid maybe the groundwater will rise.
and they'll drown.
Or maybe a bunch of nutjobs will bust out
through the top and let the poison in.
We've always been
one catastrophic failure away
from the end of it all.
and this just makes everyone
conscious of it.
Maybe that's not a bad thing.
Makes you appreciate the day you have.
I know you think
appointing Nichols is a mistake.
but something about her makes me hopeful.
Hopeful enough. I might be able
to hand the reins over to someone else.
You'd consider retiring?
To do what? Sit around and knit?
Why not?
Maybe open a shop
right next to some guy who does drawings.
[chuckles]
You know I didn't come all this way
just to meet Nichols.
I wanted to spend time with you.
[Marnes breathes shakily]
[chuckles]
[exhales heavily]
I know it's why I came.
[tools buzzing]
[metallic thudding]
[Mechanical worker] Fuck! Boss! Boss!
It's overheating
way faster than we thought.
[Knox] How much time?
A few minutes. maybe?
[Knox] Jules. you gotta get out!
We only got a few minutes! Jules!
What? What did he say?
- We only have a few minutes.
- What? No.
No. Knox. We need more time!
- We're redlining!
- Already?
The temperature's higher than we expected!
I gotta open the valve!
No! Not without the rotor blade! Fuck.
[Knox] Teddy! Teddy!
- [Teddy] We're trying!
- Try harder!
- How's it looking?
- It's getting worse.
Fuck. [sighs]
Fuck.
[Juliette panting]
- [Juliette groans]
- What do we do?
Okay. Take over.
Keep working. okay?
- It's just like I taught you. okay?
- All right.
When the blade comes up.
you get it in there. you bolt it in place.
Make sure to get the angle right
or we're screwed.
- But I can't do this with... [stammers]
- No. no. no. Look at me.
You're ready. You can do it. okay?
[sighs] Okay. [breathing heavily]
Teddy!
- Another minute!
- He needs it now!
- Get it up there!
- I'm trying!
- Jules. where are you going?
- Gonna try and buy us more time!
[breathes shakily]
Shit!
[groans]
I got it in here. You go make sure
she doesn't do anything stupid.
[grunts]
[screams. grunts]
Jules? What are you doing?
It's the only way to cool it down.
When I yell. turn it on.
You're going in there?
[Juliette panting]
Fuck. [grunting]
- [steam hissing]
- [Juliette cries out]
[Juliette groans]
Now! Turn it on!
[Juliette grunting. shouting]
[Knox] We're cooling down.
Fuck yes. Jules! It's working.
Okay. Okay. okay. okay. You crazy bitch.
[grunting]
- [steam hissing]
- [whimpering]
[Juliette pants]
[Hank] Uh. stay inside. please. sir.
Thank you.
[elderly Silo resident]
Help! Somebody. help!
Help! Help!
Somebody. help! Help!
I was trying to get home.
and the lights went out.
It's okay. sir. We got you now. Here.
Beson'll get you back safe.
[grunts] Thanks.
[Juliette straining]
[straining]
[tool buzzes]
Teddy. the blade!
[Teddy] Another minute!
[Knox] Shit. shit.
Come on. Come on. Jules.
Just give me a few more minutes. Come on.
[Juliette groaning. panting]
Come on!
Boss! Knox!
[Cooper] Teddy. hurry the fuck up!
[Teddy] Nearly there!
[screams]
[whimpers. groans] Fuck.
Coming in.
[Knox] Faster! We're redlining again!
Get it up!
Come on! [groans]
[Mechanical worker] Jules!
The blade's goin' up to Coop!
Stop. stop! I got it!
[Juliette screaming. struggles]
Come on! [groans]
Hurry!
Knox!
- [slams surface]
- Fuck.
[Knox] Cooper!
Get that blade on! It's gonna blow!
[Cooper grunting]
[Knox] Come on. Coop!
You gotta get it up there!
[Knox grunts]
[grunts. pants]
Shirley! Come on!
[Mechanical worker]
Fuck! She's still in there!
We need to get her out! Fuck!
[Knox] Fuck! [grunts]
Come on!
[groaning]
[Juliette] Come on!
Come on! [grunts] Help!
[whispering] Come on. Jules.
Just give me a few more seconds.
[muffled screams]
[grunts] Fuck.
Cooper! Get the fuck out now!
I'm almost there!
Get her out! We need to get her out!
Boss. she's drowning!
[grunting]
Come on.
[grunts. pants]
Done!
Get him down! Get Jules out now!
- Come on!
- Fuck.
[Mechanical worker] Go! Get her out!
Grab it! Pull!
- Jules?
- Come on!
Come on!
Fuck.
[grunts]
[groans]
[coughing]
- [coughs]
- She's out! Chamber is clear!
[coughing]
[gasps. panting]
[Juliette coughing]
[gasps]
- Did they get it done?
- Yeah. maybe... I think so.
[softly] Come on.
[mechanical humming]
[engineers cheering]
[pants] Fuck. Ah. fuck. Fuck.
[cheering continues]
[machinery powering up]
Hope you're not expecting me
to praise you for doing your job.
I came to say I'm sorry for what I said.
You weren't wrong.
I haven't left this place in a long time.
Yeah. but I failed.
and I... I took it out on you.
How did you fail?
I tried to do what George wanted me to.
and I... I couldn't.
You know. when I first
heard about you and the computer guy.
I... [inhales sharply]
I didn't know what to think.
And then Shirley told me
he made you smile.
Yeah.
I'm sorry you didn't get to meet him.
Oh... He didn't tell you?
No. it's all right. I told him not to.
I sent for him. I said I had a problem
with my computer.
which I didn't 'cause I built it.
When he got here. I told him if he did
anything to hurt you.
he would vanish without a trace.
[chuckling] You... [inhales sharply]
Um. before I go...
To take up a job you're
clearly unqualified to do.
Wow. I've always enjoyed
your words of encouragement.
What is that?
I don't know.
I found it with George's stuff.
You brought a relic into my workshop?
You love finding out how things work.
I also like not dying.
They wouldn't send you out to clean.
The only way you'll get out of this place
is feet first.
Thanks.
Anyway. if you get a minute.
can you try and figure out what it is?
Sure.
Thanks.
[sighs] Yeah. Um... [breathes deeply]
[exhales heavily]
Okay.
Um. thanks...
- for everything.
- Mm-hmm.
[chuckles]
I'll send messages.
Sheriff gets a radio. I'll be listening.
Yeah. of course you will.
One more thing.
[inhales sharply. sighs]
Don't end up like George.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Jahns sighs] Could I get some water?
Yes.
[Jahns sighs]
Mayor Jahns.
please tell me why this Silo
spent last night in the dark.
- Because it was night.
- That's helpful. Deputy. Thank you.
It was crucial we fix the generator.
I made the call.
You made a deal with Juliette Nichols.
our soon-to-be sheriff?
How did you hear that. Bernard?
She's a thief from Mechanical.
She'll be great.
Ten thousand lives. Ruth.
[inhales deeply]
And all the generations that follow that.
I pray to the Founders you're right.
It's strange. I haven't left Mechanical
since I got here.
It is time. There's some stuff
you gotta face up there.
[sighs] Yeah.
And when you get sick of the up-toppers.
get your ass back down here.
We'll be waiting for a visit
from our sheriff.
[scoffs]
Come on.
[sighs]
You're gonna be great.
[exhales sharply] Yeah. Okay.
Go.
[Juliette]
What about finding out the truth?
When I find something. I will. uh...
I'll send word.
A signal.
I promise.
I hope you're not making
a horrible mistake.
I'm not. [breathes deeply]
- Are you all right? Yeah?
- [breathes deeply] Mmm. I'm fine.
You sure?
[breathing deeply. inhales shakily]
Why don't you grab a bottle of wine
and take me back to my apartment?
Yes. ma'am.
[breathes deeply]
I just have to go to the restroom.
- [door closes]
- [Marnes exhales sharply]
[chuckles]
- [Marnes] Which one?
- [Jahns] Whatever you want.
[Marnes] Uh...
Hey. Ruth. you think one bottle's enough?
Maybe I get two. huh? [chuckles]
We...
Ruth.
[quietly] Ruth?
[objects clattering]
Ruth!
Ruth.
Ruth. Ruth!
[panting. grunting]
[breathes shakily]
[grunting. groaning]
Ruth!
Ruth.
- What happened? Oh...
- [moaning]
- Ruth. Oh. no.
- [choking]
Help!
Somebody. please!
Somebo... Somebody! Somebody!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm